//------------------------------------------------  Questions Array  ----------------------------------------------//
let questionSheet = [{
    question: "How many MOONS are there in our Solar System?",
    answers: {
        a: "A - 14",
        b: "B - 167",
        c: "C - 288"
    },
    correctAnswer: "C - 288"
},
{
    question: "Who fired first?",
    answers: {
        a: "A - Han Solo",
        b: "B - The Lone Gunman",
        c: "C - There was a gunshot?"
    },
    correctAnswer: "A - Han Solo"
},
{
    question: "How many primary attributes are there in Dungeons and Drangons?",
    answers: {
        a: "A - 5",
        b: "B - 6",
        c: "C - 8"
    },
    correctAnswer: "B - 6"
},
{
    question: "How many sides on a dodecahedron?",
    answers: {
        a: "A - 6",
        b: "B - 10",
        c: "C - 12"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
},
{
    question: "Which was the Greek God of the Sun",
    answers: {
        a: "A - Apollo",
        b: "B - Helios",
        c: "C - Jupiter"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
},
{
    question: "What is mycology?",
    answers: {
        a: "A - the study of mice.",
        b: "B - the study of microscopes.",
        c: "C - the study on funghi."
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
},
{
    question: "What do you call a man with a car on his head?",
    answers: {
        a: "A - Jack",
        b: "B - not going anywhere.",
        c: "C - awaiting serious medical attention."
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
},
{
    question: "Why do I wait for my dad jokes to fully mature?",
    answers: {
        a: "A - The smell... dear Stars, it's for the smell!!!",
        b: "B - Because then they're fully GROAN...",
        c: "C - Just... nope..."
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
},
{
    question: "What is the first letter of the Alphabet?",
    answers: {
        a: "A - A",
        b: "B - B",
        c: "C - C"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
},
{
    question: "How many types (classes) of star are there in the Min Sequesce?",
    answers: {
        a: "A - 5",
        b: "B - 7",
        c: "C - 9"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
},
{
    question: "Who is considered to have been the creator of The Batman?",
    answers: {
        a: "A - Bill Cold",
        b: "B - Bob Noble",
        c: "C - Bob Kane"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
},
{
    question: "IN what year was the Battle of Hastings?",
    answers: {
        a: "A - 1066",
        b: "B - 1068",
        c: "C - 1201"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
},
{
    question: "What are the nme of the moons of Mars?",
    answers: {
        a: "A - Phobos & Phoebe",
        b: "B - Dominus & Pheobe",
        c: "C - Phobos & Deimos"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
},
{
    question: "What is eisoptrophobia?",
    answers: {
        a: "A - the ferar of ice",
        b: "B - the frar of mirrors",
        c: "C - the fear of isolation"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
},
{
    question: "What do you call a man with a crane on his head?",
    answers: {
        a: "A - Dead",
        b: "B - Very strong",
        c: "C - Whatever he wants to be called."
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
},
{
    question: "Who invented Roleplaying Games?",
    answers: {
        a: "A - Gary Gygax",
        b: "B - Dave Arneson",
        c: "C - Gary & Dave"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
},
];